International Fur and Leather Workers Union Records 5676
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Berry, George L. (President International Printing Pressmen and Assistants Union), 1936-1937 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  re testimonial dinner for Berry; telegram from Berry to Lucci re GM sit-down strikes and other misc.
- Black, Walter (organizer), 1942 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Bobrowicz, Edmund (organizer), 1942 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Boerum, Mark (organizer), 1936 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Boerum, Mark, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  January-May; 2 p. report of organizing in Pennsylvania; correspondence re organizing in Winnipeg, Local 91; and routine.
- Boeram, Mark, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  May-June; 3 p. report and other correspondence on strike situation in Winnipeg; and routine.
- Boerum, Mark, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  June-December; correspondence on Winnipeg situation; 3 p. confidential letter to Boerum from Gold suggesting the strike must go on, tactics, instructions, etc. and Boerum's reply; much correspondence re Winnipeg situation; correspondence re strike situation in Seattle; and routine.
- Boerum, Mark, 1938-1939 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  routine correspondence.
- Bookkeepers and Stenographers Union, 1936-1937 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Boudin, Louis B. (Fur Workers Attorney), 1937-1940 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  re routine legal matters and payment of same.
- Boyle, Daniel (Secretary-Treasurer, Leather Workers Division), 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  routine correspondence - includes Vol. 1, No. 1 issue of U. S. Leather Worker published by U. S. Leather Co.; form letter and memo to all locals re the passing of the Smith Bill by the House of Representatives, an analysis of the bill, etc.
- Boyle, Daniel, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  June-October; routine financial correspondence
- Boyle, Daniel, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  routine financial and routine.
- Bradow, George (organizer), 1942 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  March 16th; report of organizing activities in Milwaukee.
- Brown, Edwin (organizer: Philadelphia and Camden, New Jersey), 1940 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Brown, Edwin (organizer: Wilmington, Delaware), 1941 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Brown, Edwin (organizer: Wilmington, Delaware), 1942 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Brownstone, Frank (organizer: Detroit; Atlantic City; Providence; Danbury, Connecticut), 1937-1939 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Brownstone, Frank (organizer: Philadelphia and Wilmington), 1940-1945 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  3 p. statement of Fur Workers re its dispute with American Lace Co.; and routine.
- Brownsville Labor Lyceum, 1936-1937 (Box 7, Folder 50)
- Bruno, Joseph (organizer: Wilmington, Delaware), 1942 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- Burns, Paul (organizer: Chicago, Local 43), 1939-1941 (Box 7, Folder 52)
- Burns, Paul (organizer: Chicago, Local 43), 1939-1941 (Box 7, Folder 53)
- Burt, Sam (Manager, Joint Board of Fur and Leather), 1941 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  2 telegrams re problems between Local 64 and I. J. Fox, Inc.
- Butkowitz, Samuel, 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  routine correspondence and photograph.
- B General, 1924-1955 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Includes minutes of a conference held 2/2/39, 2/11/39; form letters re Harry Bridges' deportation case, 1/29/45; letter to B. Gold From B. Baraz re removal of Baraz' name from the ballot, 6/27/45; letter of support to B. Gold re verdict in his court case from Harry Bridges, President of the International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union, 4/9/54; and routine correspondence.
- B General, 1924-1955 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- B General, 1924-1955 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- B General, 1924-1955 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- B General, 1924-1955 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Committee for Industrial Organization (CIO), 1936 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  form letters; pamphlet "To Democratic Nominees for National House of Representatives," 1936, 64 p.
- CIO, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  Includes copy of "CIO Organizers Bulletin," Vol. 1, No. 2 and 3; letter to B. Gold from John L. Lewis re monthly per capita tax to CIO, 6/7/37; "The General Executive Board Endorsed the Demands of the New York Fur Workers," no date, 11 p.; "C. I. O. Executive Adopts Important Decisions - `All or None,'" no date, 4 p.
- CIO, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- CIO, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- CIO, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  requests and invoices for pamphlets and routine correspondence.
- CIO, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- CIO, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- CIO, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- CIO, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- CIO, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  Telegram and form letter from Philip Murray, President of the CIO, urging all affiliates to support confirmation of Henry A. Walker as Secretary of Commerce 1/24/45; letter from UAW to B. Gold re shortage of leather shoes for civilians 6/2/45; and routine.
- CIO, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  form letters; President Philip Murray statement war production 1/12/45; statements and form letters re bills before Congress; resolutions; memo on handling of Jurisdictional disputes 7/1/45; and routine.
- CIO, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- CIO, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- CIO - Greater New York CIO Council, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  includes digests of Council minutes, memos, form letters re CIO stand on legislation and routine.
- CIO - Greater New York CIO Council, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- CIO - War Chest, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  routine correspondence from Jacob S. Potofsky, Chairman, New York Labor War Chest, CIO section, to B. Gold form letter including financial report of CIO War Chest.
- Cammer, Harold I. (attorney), 1953-1956 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  routine legal correspondence; letter to B. Gold re the International Union being a party to collective bargaining agreements 5/18/53; correspondence re Michigan Tanning Co., 11/4/53; letter including a copy of a proposed supplemental agreement between Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America (MCBW) and International Fur and Leather Workers Union (IFLWU) 1/11/55; correspondence re IFLWU retirement fund being transferred to the MCBW 3/8/55.
- Cammer, Harold I. (attorney), 1953-1956 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Cammer, Harold (attorney), 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 24a)
  legal documents and correspondence re legal activities - includes summary testimonies of Henrietta Schaffner and George Kleinman; legal documents re Ben Gold case; 12 p. newspaper "The Frame-up Trial of Ben Gold"; and misc.
- Cammer, Harold, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 24b)
  additional legal documents re Cammer charged with allegedly making illegal attempts concerning the Grand Jury; additional documents re Ben Gold; and other misc. legal documents.
- Cammer, Harold, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 24c)
  legal documents and correspondence re IFLWU vs. Guy Farmer, Chairman, National Labor Relations Board (NLRB); 12 p. release "Remarks of Guy Farmer."
- Cammer, Harold, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 24d)
  legal documents and correspondence; "Statement of Ben Gold on His Resignation as President of the International Fur and Leather Workers Union;" and other misc.
- Canadian Congress of Labour, 1941-1942 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  routine correspondence re receipt of per capita payments on Canadian membership.
- Canadian Congress of Labour, 1941-1942 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Chakrin, Sol, 1939-1941 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Chamouris, Charles, 1940-1941 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Churka, John, 1939-1940 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Cohen, J. L., 1938-1945 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  correspondence re legal case in Toronto, 1938; Winnipeg judgment, 1940; various other Canadian legal cases; and routine.
- Cohen, J. L., 1938-1945 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Colow, Maury, 1941-1942 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Colow, Maury, 1941-1942 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  routine
- Conference Committee of the Fur Industry, 1925 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  letter from Paul Abelson, acting Chairman, calling a special meeting 7/8/25; minutes of a meeting 9/25/25.
- Convention delegates credential, 1942-1955 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  lists of per capita payments of locals and number of delegates.
- Cook, Walter, 1936-1939 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  audit of payroll, 1/20/36; financial reports; routine correspondence.
- Cook, Walter, 1936-1939 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Cook, Walter, 1936-1939 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Corsi, Peter, 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  includes a report on organizing effort in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania; and routine correspondence.
- Council on African Affairs, 1945-1954 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  form letters; braodsides; letters from Paul Robeson to B. Gold requesting a contribution and stating indignation over the "legal frame-up action brought against you," 3/18/54.
- Couturier, W., 1937-1942 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  includes report on organizing effort in Quebec City, Quebec; and routine correspondence.
- Couturier, W., 1937-1942 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Couturier, W., 1937-1942 (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Couturier, W., 1937-1942 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Coyle, Stephen, 1941-1955 (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Crandall, Don (organizer), 1942 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- C General, 1923-1936 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  letter from editor of Cigar Makers' Official Journal, 3/30/23, making reference to a letter mailed to the editor of Freiheit; telegram to California State Federation of Labor from Lucchi requesting the removal of armed forces from the strike area of Salinas and lettuce workers and reply from the Governor of California; and routine.
- C General, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- C General, 1938-1939 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- C General, 1940-1941 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- C General, 1942-1954 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Dermer, Morris - 5 p. "Testimony of Morris Dermer." (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Dressing and Dyeing Department, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- D General, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  correspondence re situation of fur industry in Detroit; and routine.
- D General, 1938-1939 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- D General, 1940-1942 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- D General, 1945-1954 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- E General, 1936-1938 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- E General, 1939-1945 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Federman, Max (8th Vice-President), 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  7 p. report to General Executive Board meeting, 12/7/37, re Toronto Fur Workers; correspondence re investigation of misappropriation of funds by Locals 40 and 100, Toronto, including Federman; 15 p. report of the investigation which condemned Federman and others.
- Feigelman, Hyman (9th Vice-President), 1940 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Feinglass, Abe (13th Vice-President; Manager Local 45, Chicago; organizer: Midwest), 1937 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  correspondence - situation in Milwaukee, Detroit, and St. Louis re organizing, working conditions, strikes, negotiations,etc.; and routine.
- Feinglass, Abe (13th Vice-President; Manager Local 45, Chicago; organizer: Midwest), 1938 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Feinglass, Abe (13th Vice-President; Manager Local 45, Chicago; organizer: Midwest), 1939-1940 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Feinglass, Abe (13th Vice-President; Manager Local 45, Chicago; organizer: Midwest), 1941 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Feinglass, Abe (7th Vice-President), 1942 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  includes financial statements for midwest locals and correspondence - situation in Milwaukee, Detroit, and St. Louis re organizing, working conditions, strikes, negotiations,etc.; and routine.
- Feinglass, Abe (President), 1945-1954 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  letter, 6/2/45, to Gold re luggage campaign, organization of a plant in Chicago, Ohio Leather Co., and situation in Minnesota, Detroit and Cincinnati; 7 p. "Speech of Abe Feinglass to Wisconsin Tanners' Production Council, 10/31/52"; letter to Feinglass from Gold, 1/18/50, re the trial (Gold's), setting up a conference of the fur locals on the excise tax and other matterresident) - 7 p. report to General Executive Board meeting, 12/7/37, re Toronto Fur Workers; correspondence re investigation of misappropriation of funds by Locals 40 and 100, Toronto, including Federman; 15 p. report of the investigation which condemned Federman and others.
- Feinglass, Abe - includes reports re midwest locals. (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Feldman, Harry (organizer: Montreal), 1939 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Feldman, Harry, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Feldman, Harry, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Feldman, Harry, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Flemington, New Jersey, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  list of fur workers in Flemington.
- Flier, Jules (organizer: St. Louis), 1940 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Flier, Jules, 1941-1942 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Freedman, Samuel (organizer: New York City), 1941-1942 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Freiheit, 1923-1947 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  correspondence, articles, etc. re editorials by M. Olgin, editor, in Freiheit, attacking the Furriers Union; transcript of proceedings "Investigation in re Publication Against Furriers Union." (Some not translated.)
- Freiman, Nathan (7th Vice-President), 1936-1941 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Fur and Leather Worker, 1945-1947 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  letter from Ben Gold to Executive Board members, 10/31/45, re making the publication as good as possible and asking for ideas, criticisms, etc. and replies.
- Fur Vest Project, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  routine letter.
- Fur Worker, 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  form letters re monthly publication and routine correspondence.
- Fur Worker, 1939-1940 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- F General, 1936-1937 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  correspondence between Lucchi and Fur Floor Boys and Shipping Clerks Union of New York requesting a charter; correspondence re Furriers' Social Club in New York City; 2 p. Newsletter of Furriers Trade Union League; correspondence (form letters) re defense fund for Ferrero and Sallitto (deportation cases); correspondence with Fur Salesmen's Guild; and routine.
- F General, 1938-1939 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  correspondence with Fur Dressers and Dyers Board of Trade, Inc. re lowering tariffs and routine.
- F General, 1940-1941 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- F General, 1942-1947 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  appeal letter and proposal from Father Flanagan's Boys' Home re proposal for an "American Labor Memorial"; Farmers Educational and Cooperative Union of America to Gold re increased participation of Fur Workers during meeting in eastern Pennsylvania (Farmer-labor rally); telegram and correspondence re tobacco workers strike in North Carolina, 1947; letter to Albert Fitzgerald, President of the United Electrical Workers re anti-Semitic propaganda at home and abroad; and routine.
- F General, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  release and broadside re Food, Tobacco, and Agricultural Workers Local 22 strike against R. J. Reynolds (no date); letter from Howard Fast asking for help in selling his latest book "Silas Timberman"; and routine.
- Galanos, Thomas, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Galanos, Thomas, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Gallant, Clifford, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- General Executive Board, 1936-1940 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  misc. correspondence re suspension of Vice-President John Apostol, 11/36; notification of meetings; form letters; letter from Harry Feldman, organizer, to P. Lucchi, 6/10/40, re activities in Quebec City; and routine.
- General Executive Board, 1936-1940 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- General Executive Board, 1936-1940 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- General Executive Board, 1936-1940 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- General Executive Board, 1936-1940 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- General Executive Board, 1936-1940 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- General Executive Board, 1936-1940 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- General Executive Board, 1936-1940 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Gmeiner, Charles, 1925-1927 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Gold, Ben, 1937-1947 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  letter from S. Moskowitz asking Gold to endorse his application for re-entry to the Communist Party, 5/30/37; letter from Gold to P. Lucchi detailing Seattle, Washington strike situation 7/25/37, 7/29/37; speech delivered by Gold at "Veto Rally" at Madison Square Garden, 6/10/47, against Taft-Hartley Act; copy of letter to Federman, 8th Vice-President, instructing him to return missing money to Unemployment Insurance Fund and suspending him (no date); signed decision by the General Executive Board acting as a Trial Committee re John Apostol, 10th Vice-President, 1/26/37.
- Gold, Ben, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  Defense Committee - article "The Attack on Ben Gold," no date; copy of letter from B. Gold to International Executive Board members re his upcoming trial, 1/12/54; form letters; resolutions; minutes of meetings of Trade Union Committee for the Defense of Ben Gold; letters of support; "Notes of Gold Defense Committee," no date, 2 p.; court document.
- Gold, Ben, 1945-1954 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  form letters re establishment of Veteran's and Servicemen's Committee re November 15, 1945 national leather workers' work stoppage; statement of Ben Gold on his resignation as President of the IFLWU, 10/2/54.
- Gold, Ben Freiheit, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  constitution and by-laws of Morning Freiheit Association, Inc.; form letter; articles by Gold to Morning Freiheit re fascism 2/6/45.
- Gold, Ben Personal, 1945-1947 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  routine personal correspondence (some Yiddish).
- Gold, Ben Personal, 1945-1947 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Gold, Ben Personal, 1945-1947 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Goldman, J. D., 1936-1937 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Goldstein, Harold broadside, 1935-1937 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  letter to P. Lucchi re situation in Detroit, Michigan, 6/6/36; report on new agreement with Cleveland Wholesale Furriers, 6/7/37; and routine correspondence.
- Goldstein, Harold broadside, 1935-1937 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Gordon, J., 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Graff, Lloyd, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  letter from P. Lucchi re import tariffs on furs, 3/1/38, and related correspondence.
- Grodsky, David M., 1936-1937 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- G General, 1936-1954 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- G General, 1936-1954 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- G General, 1936-1954 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- G General, 1936-1954 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Harris, Moe, 1936-1938 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  letter from the workers of Queens Premier Fur Dressing Co., Local 48, to P. Lucchi re removal of business agent Moe Harris, Easton, Pennsylvania, 3/5/37; and routine.
- Herbin, Robert, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Herbst, Samuel, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  correspondence re a judgment against Herbst and 35 other defendants as a result of the fur strike in Winnipeg, Canada, in 1936; and routine.
- Herbst, Samuel, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Hirshfield, Victor, 1940-1942 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Hirshfield, Victor, 1940-1942 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Hirshfield, Victor, 1940-1942 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Hirshfield, Victor, 1940-1942 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Hirshfield, Victor, 1940-1942 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- History of the Union (Box 10, Folder 38)
  memo on tentative arrangements for publication of history of our union, 4 p.
- Hollander, A. and Son, 1943-1954 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  pamphlet entitled "Your Group Insurance Plan" 16 p., 1944; article, form letters and correspondence between Ben Gold and Local 140, Montreal, re strike and Gold's urging members "to return to work at once," 1945; a report to sub-committee of the General Executive Board on "The Problems of Hollander Local 140 of Newark, N.J.," 7/19/45; and misc.
- Hollander, A. and Son, 1943-1954 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  pamphlet entitled "Your Group Insurance Plan" 16 p., 1944; article, form letters and correspondence between Ben Gold and Local 140, Montreal, re strike and Gold's urging members "to return to work at once," 1945; a report to sub-committee of the General Executive Board on "The Problems of Hollander Local 140 of Newark, N.J.," 7/19/45; and misc
- Hollander, A. and Son, 1943-1954 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- H General, 1933-1960 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  form letters; requests for donations to various organizations; and routine.
- H General, 1933-1960 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- H General, 1933-1960 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Indusco, Inc., 1947 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  corrsepondence; Indusco Bulletin, Vol. VII, No. 7-8; "Industrial Cooperative Movement in Shantung Liberated Area" by Shueh Muo-Kiao, 10 p.
- I. W. W. General Defense Committee, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  form letter.
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW), 1926 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  correspondence re organizing information.
- International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGWU), 1927-1936 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  letter to Lucchi from organizer of Cloakmakers Union, Local 216, ILGWU re situation in Winnipeg, 9/19/36; and routine.
- ILGWU, 1937-1939 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  letter to David Dubinsky, President of ILGWU, re Winnipeg situation and asking him not to renew contract with a particular company because they would not bargain with Fur Workers; and routine.
- Isserman, Morris (union attorney), 1937-1942 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  routine re professional services.
- Italy, 1945-1946 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  list of proposals re meeting on relief to Italy and misc. list and correspondence.
- I General, 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- I General, 1938-1939 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- I General, 1940-1942 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- I General, 1945-1954 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Jewish Campaigns, 1928-1945 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  correspondence, announcements, bulletins re various conferences, meetings, fund raising from various groups.
- Jewish Daily Forward, 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  release re member of Local 70 (Greek local) beaten; and routine.
- J General, 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- J General, 1938-1941 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- J General, 1942-1954 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Kalmikoff, Hyman (Treasurer of International), 1937 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  re Kalmikoff's illness and personal.
- Karlin, "Comrade, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  correspondence between Fur Workers and Socialist party re remarks made by Karlin about Fur Workers Organization during his campaign for 14th Congressional District, New York City.
- Kaufman, Morris (Box 11, Folder 16)
  two telegrams re union activities.
- Klancer, Rudolph (organizer: Local 44, Gowanda, New York), 1942 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Klig, Myer (National Organizer: Canada, organizer: Minneapolis), 1937-1938 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  letter reporting situation in Toronto, Montreal and Quebec City; letters reporting Minneapolis situation (Local 71); and routine.
- Klig, Myer, 1939-1941 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Klig, Myer (Vice-President), 1942-1947 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  signed petitions by employees of Yaeger's Furs Ltd. (Local 91, Winnipeg) to join Union; correspondence between Klig and Muni Taub (organizer: Local 91) re activities; between Klig and Mr. Sable of Sable Ltd. re problems with workers; correspondence re Klig and Immigration and Naturalization Service; 5 p. "Report of M. Klig," no date; and routine.
- Kovacic, Frank (organizer: Wilmington, Delaware), 1941-1942 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Kretchman, Louis, 1938-1939 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Krowcheck, Paul (organizer: Toronto, Ontario; President, Oshawa Leather Workers Union, Local 205), 1941-1942 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- K General, 1936-1939 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  letter from member of Local 70 re an appeal; and routine.
- K General, 1950-1954 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  9 p. article by Henry Klein on the "Marshall Plan"; and routine.
- Labor's Non-Partisan League (LNPL), 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  5 p. speech of John L. Lewis, 8/10/36; to Lucchi, member, National Executive Board of LNPL, from George Berry, President re full support of Senator Robert LaFollette; backing of Roosevelt's program for reforming the Federal judiciary; 6 p. address of Senator Robert LaFollette re judiciary reform; and routine.
- LNPL, 1937-1940 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Lancaster, Roy (organizer: Detroit), 1941-1942 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Lancaster, Roy (organizer: Detroit), 1941-1942 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Lehman, Herbert H., 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  telegram from Lucchi protesting bill passed by New York State Assembly re depriving the American Labor Party from being officially recognized in coming municipal elections; and routine.
- Lewis, Leo (organizer: Newark, Buffalo, New Haven, Toronto, Gloversville), 1938-1941 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Lewis, Leo (organizer: Newark, Buffalo, New Haven, Toronto, Gloversville), 1938-1941 (Box 11, Folder 32)